Class of 1958 Records, 1954-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1958 Records
1954-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1958.
RG 80 UUID:6d2e59b8-1e8f-44a1-96b6-68588f3fbe20
5 boxes (3.33 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1958.
The Class of 1958 was the eightieth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1958 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1958, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1958 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1958 (Box 2212, Folder 1)
- Commencement-Photographs 1958 (Box 2212, Folder 2)
- Commencement-Speaker: John F. Kennedy 1958 (Box 2212, Folder 3)
- Freshman Handbook 1954-1955 (Box 2212, Folder 4)
- Freshman Prom 1955 (Box 2212, Folder 5)
- General 1957 (Box 2212, Folder 6)
- Groups 1954-1958, undated (Box 2212, Folder 7)
- Ivy Day 1958 (Box 2212, Folder 8)
- Class Letters 1957-1976, 2002 (Box 2212, Folder 9)
- Officer Photographs 1955 (Box 2212, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1963 (Box 2212, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1968 (Box 2212, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1973-1978 (Box 2212, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1983 (Box 2212, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1993-2003 (Box 2212, Folder 15)
- Songs 1957 (Box 2212, Folder 16)
- Who's Who 1954 (Box 2212, Folder 17)